SARA ADI

sara_adi@hotmail.ca | (647)-470-4382 | 4522 Penhallow Rd. Mississauga, ON, L5V 1E7

OBJECTIVE

Analytical-minded and creative team player with a strong background in designing, planning, and maintenance of software programs. Interested in applying my technical skills and expertise along with designing creative software and products as per the clients' needs and enhance the reputation of your organization.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computing in Software Engineering

SEPT. 2020 - APR. 2024

University of Guelph, Guelph ON

Anticipated Courses in Programming (C, Java), Software Design, Data Structures, Microcomputers

- Minor in Project Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

Advisor July, 2018 - PRESENT

FGL Sportchek | Pickering, ON

- Organized and reported on financial information to document payment histories and assist with sound financial accounting.
- Mentored new team members on POS system operation, customer service strategies and sales goals.

INVOLVEMENT

President MAR. 2021 - PRESENT

Guelph University School of Computing/Information Science (SOCIS) | Guelph ON

- Alongside my Executive team, I aid in providing insight into the struggles students within the college face and how to bring forth action to create a more sustainable learning environment, through acting as the student representative in Governance meetings, and committees.
- Responsible for innovating new ideas within the student government which would appeal to the majority of +1500 students to ensure a memorable school experience and creating a supportive culture.

Teen Ambassador JUNE. 2019 - SEPT. 2020

Canada Learning Code | Toronto ON

- Lead multiple discussions and communicated with industry experts and technology influencers to gain insight on different disciplines within computing and business.
- Organized and attended workshops to strengthen my knowledge and skills of HTML and CSS. While also directing my learning to other like-minded females.

Director of Affairs MAR. 2019 - FEB. 2020

Mississauga Youth Action Committee | Mississauga ON

- Responsible for ensuring every member worked collaboratively with one another, planned events, and connected with the city's youth regularly to foster community growth and outreach.
- Voice the concerns youth hold in the city and bring forth action through working with the mayor and stakeholders